There are no shortcuts to living your dreams.
Clika is a drama, music film directed by Michael Greene.
Aspiring small-town musician Chito is determined to make it big.
When a clip of him performing one of his songs goes viral, he seizes the opportunity and pushes
to carve out a place for himself in the new wave of Mexican-American music...
and ultimately gets caught in a game more dangerous than anticipated.
Chito, played by Jay Dee.
Alfredo, played by Cristian E. Gutierrez.
Blunt, played by Daniel 'DoKnows' Lopez.
Candy, played by Laura Lopez.
Mari, played by Nana Ponceleon.
This is a list of American films that are scheduled for release in 2026.
Following the box office section, this list is organized chronologically, providing information
on release dates, production companies, directors, and principal cast members.
The tone is emotional.